http://www.mountaindesigns.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Our privacy commitment The Spotlight Retail Group (‘SRG’) is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information or personal data, as defined below (hereafter referred to, collectively, as “personal information”). We strive to manage your personal information in an open and transparent way.This Policy applies to all of the entities within the Spotlight Retail Group, including but not limited to Spotlight Pty Ltd (ACN 005 180 861), Anaconda Group Pty Ltd (ACN 107 364 563), Mountain Design Holdings Pty Ltd (ACN 627 475 085), Spotlight Ltd (NZ Company No. 553661) and Spotlight Pte Ltd (Singapore UEN No. 199504543C). In this Policy ‘we’, ‘us’, ‘our’ and ‘SRG’ refers the Spotlight Retail Group.SRG will only use your personal information when it is necessary for us to deliver you a service or perform other necessary business functions and activities.SRG will not use or disclose your personal information for purposes unrelated to the services we provide, unless we first obtain your consent.This policy is structured so that you can view information relevant to you if you are a: CustomerEmployeeSupplier Our Privacy Obligations This Privacy Policy sets out how we comply
with our obligations under the Privacy Act 1988;Privacy Act 1993 (New Zealand);
andPersonal Data Protection Act 2012 (Singapore). SRG is bound by the requirements of these laws, which regulates
how we may collect, use, disclose and/or store personal information. These laws also specify how individuals may access and correct personal
information held about them. “Personal Information" (as defined in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and Privacy Act 1993 (New
Zealand)) means information or an opinion about an identified individual (or an individual who is reasonably identifiable), whether true or
not, or recorded in a material form or not. For example, these types of information could include your name, contact details, age and health
information. “Personal data" (as defined in the Personal Data Protection Act (Singapore)) means data, whether true or not,
about an individual who can be identified from that data, or from that data and other information to which the organisation has or is likely to
have access. If you have any questions regarding SRG's Privacy Policy, please call us on 1300 305 405 (Australia) or 0800 276 222 (New
Zealand) or (65) 6733 9808 (Singapore) email us at privacy@SRG.com.au. If you would like
SRG to send you a hard copy of this policy, please contact us and we will do so. By visiting our websites and/or providing your personal
information or data to us, you consent to the terms and conditions in this Privacy Policy, unless you tell us to the contrary by contacting us.
If you wish to withdraw consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information or data, please email us at privacy@SRG.com.au.  From time to time, our policies and procedures will be
reviewed and, if appropriate, updated. If any changes are made to this policy these will be posted on our websites.  Customers How and why does SRG
collect and hold your personal information?
What kind of
personal information does SRG collect and hold?
How does SRG use
your personal information?
In what
circumstances will
SRG disclose your personal information?
Who do we disclose
your personal information to?
Direct marketing
Does SRG disclose
your personal
information to overseas recipients?
Use of Government
Identifiers
Data quality and
Security
Website usage
Use of Cookies Links to Third Party Sites How you can access
or
correct your personal information
How you can notify
us of a privacy concern or contact our
Privacy Contact Officer   How and why does SRG collect and hold your
personal information? SRG will only collect
personal information
about you by lawful and fair means, and not in an unreasonably intrusive
manner. It is SRG’s usual practice
to collect
personal information directly from you when you: submit a Spotlight VIP club or Anaconda Adventure club registration form
or Mountain Designs Alliance Club registration form or amendment form;register with any of our other loyalty or marketing
programs;complete any online form
on one of our websites or online payment gateways;visit or use an SRG website (including any
SRG forums);subscribe to marketing and sales material or communications;complete an online form on one of our social media
channels;enter an SRG trade promotion or competition;register an SRG gift card;complete an online form on one of our
online advertisements that is
placed on a third party website;complete a hard copy form or provide information in one of our
stores;complete and return to us a hard copy form that is provided with one of
our products;complete and return to us a
wholesale account application form;request delivery of SRG products;make a purchase, return or exchange a product where we
request you to
verify your identity;speak with us, or one of our representatives directly during a product
or sales enquiry;
orcontact us directly by telephone, via mail, e-mail or online via our websites or social media channels. We may collect
personal information about
you from a third party or a publicly available source, but only if you have
consented to such collection, or would
reasonably expect us to collect your
personal information in this way.  Where we can, we will allow you to deal with
us anonymously
or by using a pseudonym. However, in some circumstances, this
may not be possible, and SRG may need to collect personal information from you
to
provide you with a delivery or other service. In some cases, if you do not
provide the required personal information we will not be able to
provide you
with a service. If we receive information about you from a
third party and it is not information we need in respect of our
business
activities, we will destroy or de-identify that information (provided it is
lawful to do so).  What kind of personal information does SRG collect and hold? Any personal information that you provide directly
or via other channels is collected and managed by SRG. If you provide your personal information to
a third party via a link from an SRG
website, that information is collected and
managed by those third parties which are not related to SRG. You should familiarise yourself with
their
privacy policy prior to deciding whether you wish to provide them with your
information. The types of personal information SRG may
collect includes your:
name; date of birth; gender; marital status and family details; residential, business and postal address; email address; contact telephone numbers; identification details; testimonials or opinions; photos of you; financial information, such as credit card details; written or verbal
contact with SRG, including voice recordings of telephone
conversations you have had with our employees; and activities, including but
not limited to lifestyle and other interests.
Whilst you may opt not to provide us with your
personal information,
you should
be
aware that without this personal information, we may not be able to provide
you with some of the services and/or products you are
seeking.If you provide us with information about any
third party, you must obtain that third party's permission to give us the
information and inform them that you have given the information to us.  How does SRG use your
personal information? We use your personal information for a
variety of reasons including, but not limited to the following:
to contact you in relation to our loyalty or marketing programs; to provide services and products to you; to answer your
inquiries and deliver customer service to you; to tell you about other products that we think may be of interest to you; to
enable us to undertake a credit assessment; to maintain and improve customer services; to manage your gift card balance; to meet our legal obligations; to consider making offers for employment purposes; to manage and resolve any legal, consumer
or commercial complaints and
issues; to carry out internal functions including training; and to conduct marketing research and
analysis.
In what circumstances will SRG disclose your
personal information? In the course of conducting our business and
providing our products and services to you, we may disclose your personal
information.
We only disclose personal information for
the purposes for which it was given to us, or for purposes which are directly
related to one
of our functions or activities.
We do not give it to anyone else unless one of the following applies:
you have consented to
the disclosure; you would reasonably expect, or have been told, that your information is
passed to those individuals, businesses or
agencies; or it is otherwise required or authorised by law.
If we engage third party agents or
contractors, we will take
all reasonable steps to ensure that they do not
breach privacy requirements in relation to the information, before we share
your personal
information with them.  Who do we disclose your personal information
to? We may disclose
your personal information
to:
another SRG business or entity; to companies that perform services on our behalf, such as
delivery
companies, data entry service providers, trade promotion or gift card
administration and account management providers; professional advisers (such as lawyers or auditors); payment systems operators and financial institutions; organisations
authorised by SRG to conduct promotional, research or
marketing activities; upon lawful request from law enforcement agencies or
government
authorities; and any persons acting on your behalf including those persons nominated by
you, executors, trustees and legal
representatives.
In all circumstances where your personal
information is disclosed, we will take all steps reasonable to ensure
that
these third parties undertake to protect your privacy.  Direct Marketing We are
committed to compliance with all laws
and requirements relating to the use of your personal information.  We will only use or disclose your
personal
information for direct marketing purposes if you have provided your information
for that purpose (and you would expect us to use the
information for that
purpose), or if you have provided consent for your information to be used in
this way. From time to time, we may
contact you with
information about products and services offered by us and our related entities
and our business partners, which we think may
be of interest to you. When we contact you it may be by mail,
telephone, email, SMS/text message or social media message. Where we use or
disclose your personal
information for the purpose of direct marketing, we will:
allow you to request not to receive direct
marketing communications
(also known as ‘opting-out’); and comply with your request to ‘opt-out’ of receiving
further
communications within a reasonable timeframe.
SRG will only ever contact you if we have obtained your consent, and you can
ask to be removed from our marketing lists at
any time by contacting us directly.  If you do not wish to be contacted by SRG,
please e-mail us at privacy@srg.com.au.  Does SRG disclose your personal information
to overseas recipients? Your personal information may be disclosed
to other SRG entities, business partners and service providers in Australia and
overseas for the reason and limited purpose explained below. The countries this information may be
disclosed to will vary from time to time, but may include Australia, New
Zealand, Singapore, Malaysia,
Fiji, Japan, and the United States of America. Sometimes we use third party platforms and
services to process sales, provide web support,
send marketing messages,
deliver products or otherwise deliver information. These services are hosted
and managed by organisations other than
ourselves, and some of these services
are hosted overseas. We use products and services maintained in Australia, New
Zealand, Singapore,
Malaysia, Fiji, Japan, and the United States of America. Your personal information may be stored in a
secure and encrypted form overseas
(e.g. in data storage and cloud computing
facilities operated by us (or by third parties on SRG’s behalf) to prevent unauthorised access,
use, disclosure, copying, modification and disposal thereof.  Use of Government Identifiers SRG will not use Government Identifiers,
such as a driver's licence number as its own identifier of individuals.  Data Quality and Security We will take all reasonable steps to ensure
that your personal information is stored
securely and is protected from misuse
and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. The
personal information that
we collect about you is stored on our database servers
& filing systems managed by us in Australia.  Website Usage Our websites are professionally hosted and operate
in a secure environment. You should however be
aware that there is always an
inherent risk in transmitting your personal information via the Internet.We use secure payment platforms to
process online
orders in an SSL-secure environment. Customers can see their cards being debited in real time.We take website and credit
card security extremely
seriously, and always endeavour to provide a secure safe platform on which to
conduct online transactions. All our
websites use 2048- bit SSL with up to 256- bit encryption for capturing personal information and processing transactions.
We do not store your
credit card detailsTo ensure you are accessing a secure server,
check for the unbroken key or closed lock symbol located generally either
at
the bottom left or top right of your browser window. If it appears, then SSL is
active. You can double check this by looking at the URL as
well. If SSL is
active, then the first characters of that line will read ‘https’ rather than
just ‘http’. It is
important for you to protect against unauthorised access to
your password and to your computer.Ensure you logout when you have finished
visiting
our websites especially if you accessed them from a shared computer.Use of Cookies What are cookies? A cookie is a small amount of information that a
website transfers to your computer for record keeping purposes.  The data that is collected
may include IP address (or proxy server), device and application identification numbers, location,
browser type, Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, the pages and files viewed, searches,
operating system and system configuration information and date/time stamps associated with your
usage.What types of cookies do we use? There are four main types.
site functionality cookies – these allow you to navigate the site and use our features, such
as “Add to Cart” and “Add to Wishlist”; site analytics cookies –
these cookies allow us to measure and analyse how our customers use the site, to improve both its
functionality and your shopping experience; customer preference cookies – when you're
browsing or shopping on our website(s), these cookies will remember your preferences (like your
language or location), so we can make your shopping experience as seamless as possible, and more
personal to you; and targeting or advertising cookies – these are used to deliver ads
relevant to They also limit the number of times that you see an ad and help us measure the
effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.
Why do we use cookies? Cookies
help provide additional functionality to our website(s) and help us analyse site usage more accurately.
We use information collected from cookies to better understand, customise and improve user experience
with our websites, services and offerings, as well as to manage our advertising. For instance, our
server may set a cookie that keeps you from having to enter a password more than once during a visit to
one of our websites. Also, we may use web analytics services that leverage cookies to help us to
understand how visitors engage with and navigate our site (e.g. how and when pages in a site are
visited and by how many visitors). Cookies also help us provide website visitors with a more
personalized, customized and relevant experience by delivering content and functionality based on
individual preferences and interests. If you have provided us with personal information (e.g. through a
registration or a request for certain materials), we may associate this personal information with
information gathered through cookies. Cookies and Google Analytics In some cases,
the third-party service providers we work with may use cookies to support our digital marketing
initiatives.  We use Google Analytics Services, provided by Google, Inc. (Google). Google uses
cookies and similar technologies to analyse overall trends and help us to understand how users use a
website, how we can improve our websites and guarantee their security and continued proper
functioning.  The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including
your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google
will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on
website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and
internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by
law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate
your IP address with any other data held by Google. For more information about the processing of
data about you by Google, see Google's
Privacy Policy. You can prevent data being used by Google Analytics by downloading and installing
the Google Opt-Out Browser Add On provided by Google. For more information about the cookies used by
Google, see Google Analytics Cookie Usage page. How to manage cookies Your web browser can be set to allow you to control whether you will accept cookies, reject cookies
or to notify you each time a cookie is sent to your browser. If your browser is set to reject cookies,
websites that are cookie-enabled will not recognise you when you return to the website, and some
website functionality may be lost. The “Help” section of your browser may tell you how to
prevent your browser from accepting cookies. Cookies and Personal Information In
all cases in which cookies are used, the cookie will not collect personal information except with your
explicit permission. For full information on how we use and handle your data, please refer to our
Privacy Policy and our GDPR Compliance Notice (if you are an EU resident). If you:
have queries, concerns or complaints about the manner in which your personal information has been
collected or handled by SRG; or would like to request access to or correction of the personal
information we hold about you;
please write to: Australia and New Zealand: The
Privacy Officer, Legal Department, SRG Retail Group Level 6, 111 Cecil Street South Melbourne Vic 3205
Australia. Singapore: The Privacy Officer, 68 Orchard Road Plaza Singapura #05-11/19 Singapore
38839 Email: privacy@srg.com.au Phone: 1300 305 405 (Australia) or 0800 276 222 (New Zealand) or (65) 6733 9808 (Singapore). Links
to Third Party Sites Whilst links to third party websites may be provided
on our website, we are not responsible for the content or
practices of these
third-party websites.These links are provided for your convenience and
do not represent SRG's endorsement of any
linked third-party website. We
recommend that you check the privacy policies of these third parties prior to providing
them with your personal
information.No links may be made to this website without our
prior written consent.  How
you can access or correct your personal
information You can request access to the personal information
we hold about you at any time,
and we will provide you with that information unless we
are prevented by law from giving it to you. If we are unable to give you
access to the information
you have requested, we will give you reasons for this decision when we respond
to your request. You will not
be charged for accessing your
information, although we might have to charge a reasonable fee for processing your request, including
photocopying, administration and postage. We will provide you with a written estimate of any fee payable before we process your request. If you believe that your personal
information is not accurate, complete or up to date, please contact us via
the contact details below and
we will correct this information.  How you can notify us of a privacy concern or
contact our
Privacy Contact Officer If you:
have queries, concerns or complaints about the manner in which your
personal information
has been collected or handled by SRG; or would like to request access to or correction of the personal
information we hold about
you;
please write to: Australia and New Zealand: The Privacy Officer,
Legal Department, SRG Retail Group Level 6, 111 Cecil Street South Melbourne  Vic  3205 AustraliaSingapore: The
Privacy Officer, 68 Orchard Road Plaza Singapura #05-11/19 Singapore 238839Email: privacy@srg.com.auPhone: 1300 305 405 (Australia) or 0800 276 222 (New Zealand) or
(65) 6733 9808  (Singapore) If you consider your privacy concerns have not been resolved satisfactorily by us, or you
wish to obtain more information on privacy requirements, you can contact: Australia The Office of the
Australian
Information Commissioner on 1300 363 992 or visit their website at www.oaic.gov.au. New Zealand Privacy Commissioner (New Zealand) on 0800 803 909 or visit their
website at www.privacy.org.nz Singapore Personal Data
Protection Commissioner (Singapore) on +65 6377 3131
or visit their website at www.pdpc.gov.sg.  Employees SRG collects personal
information (which may
include sensitive information) from its employees (past, current and future) in
order to provide a range of employment
related services. SRG collects personal information directly
from job applicants (and their referees) or from recruitment agencies and
relates service providers.  The
information we collect may include your name, address contact details,
employment and education history,
the names of your referees and other relevant
information. This information we collect about you will
be used for evaluative purposes in
recruitment and may be disclosed to third party service
providers who provide recruitment related services to us.  This may include
overseas recruitment related
services located in Australia, New Zealand, Singapore and Malaysia.  Suppliers We collect information from our suppliers to facilitate sourcing and purchasing products and
services.  This information can be collected directly from suppliers and related service providers.  We may share supplier information
with entities located overseas in the Asia Pacific Region.
BECOME AN ALLIANCE CLUB MEMBER
Get VIP discounts, attend exclusive events and more
Join for free
